{
  "education": [
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "2017",
        "score": 0.001256554271094501
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "Syria",
        "score": 0.03595456853508949
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "various schools",
        "score": 0.16791069507598877
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "Damascus",
        "score": 0.8010872006416321
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "havo 4 until 2017",
        "score": 0.007938077673316002
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "ISK Peter Jelles",
        "score": 0.027659522369503975
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "score": 0.31393668055534363
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "ISK Peter Jelles",
        "score": 0.31390005350112915
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "ISK Peter Jelles In Leeuwarden",
        "score": 0.14966003596782684
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "ISK Peter Jelles In Leeuwarden",
        "score": 0.0003055089619010687
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "retail",
        "score": 0.00019782422168646008
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "retail",
        "score": 0.5932901501655579
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland College",
        "score": 0.06168530508875847
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "Leeuwarden",
        "score": 0.014513131231069565
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "2018 until 2019",
        "score": 0.014737380668520927
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "financial administration on level mbo2",
        "score": 0.00035860633943229914
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "financial administration",
        "score": 0.0016291553620249033
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.00016256076924037188
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.00010610333265503868
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "2018 until 2019",
        "score": 0.00022187524882610887
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "Mbo 3",
        "score": 0.0009326505823992193
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "financial administration",
        "score": 0.0023011090233922005
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.0008415032061748207
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.0008922733832150698
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "2019 until 2022",
        "score": 0.00038983594276942313
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "Mbo 4",
        "score": 0.0004946393892168999
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "financial administration",
        "score": 0.0030339525546878576
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.0008251168765127659
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "Friesland college",
        "score": 0.0004756769340019673
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "2022 until 2023",
        "score": 9.059321746462956e-5
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "degree",
        "question": "what is the degree?",
        "answer": "bachelor",
        "score": 0.22606195509433746
      },
      {
        "info": "major/field",
        "question": "what is the major/field of study?",
        "answer": "International Business",
        "score": 0.7945644855499268
      },
      {
        "info": "institution name",
        "question": "what is the name of institution?",
        "answer": "NhlStenden In Leeuwarden",
        "score": 0.12524637579917908
      },
      {
        "info": "institution location",
        "question": "where is the location of institution?",
        "answer": "NhlStenden In Leeuwarden",
        "score": 0.14996609091758728
      },
      {
        "info": "attended date",
        "question": "what is the dates attended?",
        "answer": "NhlStenden In Leeuwarden",
        "score": 8.790841093286872e-5
      }
    ]
  ],
  "experience": [
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "Shop keeper",
        "score": 0.7243465185165405
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "Althana",
        "score": 0.015534360893070698
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Althana' in Damascus Syria",
        "score": 0.387117475271225
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "2014 until 2017",
        "score": 0.4928532838821411
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Shop keeping, selling pastries",
        "score": 0.16657578945159912
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "learned how to talk with customers and how retail in general works",
        "score": 7.615875802002847e-5
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "Sales employee",
        "score": 0.6084944605827332
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "Kruidvat",
        "score": 0.05319153890013695
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Kruidvat in Leeuwarden the Netherlands",
        "score": 0.2891506552696228
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "October 2018",
        "score": 0.7143216133117676
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "filling the store and helping customers",
        "score": 0.5556685924530029
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "I learned to speak dutch and the basics of retailing in the Netherlands",
        "score": 4.8445559514220804e-5
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "Book keeper",
        "score": 0.4368150532245636
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "dambacht",
        "score": 0.0006900646258145571
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "dambacht in Leeuwarden the Netherlands",
        "score": 0.2947286069393158
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "2019",
        "score": 0.5535135865211487
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "responsible for the account book of this company",
        "score": 0.014048932120203972
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "Book keeper internship in dambacht in Leeuwarden the Netherlands",
        "score": 3.1328586374002043e-6
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "Account manager",
        "score": 0.5035509467124939
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "mother company",
        "score": 0.02433662675321102
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Leeuwarden the Netherlands",
        "score": 0.336871474981308
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "2020",
        "score": 0.5495681166648865
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "I was responsible for the connection between LIS and the mother company",
        "score": 0.0588843896985054
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "Account manager internship",
        "score": 3.980874680564739e-5
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "intern account administrator",
        "score": 0.580566942691803
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "Aegon",
        "score": 0.40086814761161804
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Leeuwarden the Netherlands",
        "score": 0.7631908059120178
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "2022 until 2023",
        "score": 0.5740461945533752
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "to manage clients' personal information and to communicate with agents",
        "score": 0.456110417842865
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "manage clients' personal information and to communicate with agents",
        "score": 0.000248232448939234
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "sales employee",
        "score": 0.759536623954773
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "ziengs (TMS)",
        "score": 0.30667388439178467
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Leeuwarden, the Netherlands",
        "score": 0.7047261595726013
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "between 2022 and 2023",
        "score": 0.3997214734554291
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "helping customers and maintaining the store",
        "score": 0.7926989793777466
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "Advice on shoe brand and sizes and circumcisions",
        "score": 0.043149758130311966
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "info": "job title",
        "question": "what is the job title?",
        "answer": "responsible for helping th customers and maintaining the store and giving advice regarding Asian products",
        "score": 0.05957939103245735
      },
      {
        "info": "company name",
        "question": "what is the company name?",
        "answer": "Toko Saigon",
        "score": 0.7363317608833313
      },
      {
        "info": "location of employment",
        "question": "where is the location of employment?",
        "answer": "Toko Saigon",
        "score": 0.8794982433319092
      },
      {
        "info": "date of employment",
        "question": "what is the date of employment?",
        "answer": "September 2023",
        "score": 0.8356881141662598
      },
      {
        "info": "Responsibilities",
        "question": "what is the Responsibilities?",
        "answer": "helping th customers and maintaining the store and giving advice regarding Asian products",
        "score": 0.5655492544174194
      },
      {
        "info": "Achievements and Accomplishments",
        "question": "what is the Achievements and Accomplishments?",
        "answer": "I learned about East Asian and Indian cuisine and culture ",
        "score": 0.00128627335652709
      }
    ]
  ]
}
